export const throws = [
    { question: 'Deashi Harai (or barai) ', answer: 'Advanced Foot Sweep' },
    { question: 'Hiza Guruma ', answer: 'Knee Wheel' },
    { question: 'Sasae Tsurikomi Ashi ', answer: 'Supporting Lift-Pull Foot' },
    { question: 'Uki Goshi ', answer: 'Floating Hip' },
    { question: 'Osoto Gari ', answer: 'Major Outer Reap' },
    { question: 'O Goshi ', answer: 'Major Hip' },
    { question: 'Ouchi Gari ', answer: 'Major Inner Reap' },
    { question: 'Seoi Nage ', answer: 'Shoulder Throw' },
    { question: 'Kosoto Gari ', answer: 'Minor Outer Reap' },
    { question: 'Kouchi Gari ', answer: 'Minor Inner Reap' },
    { question: 'Koshi Guruma', answer: 'Hip Wheel' },
    { question: 'Tsurikomi Goshi ', answer: 'Lift-Pull Hip' },
    { question: 'Okuriashi Harai ', answer: 'Assisting Foot Sweep' },
    { question: 'Tai Otoshi ', answer: 'Body Drop' },
    { question: 'Harai Goshi ', answer: 'Sweeping Hip' },
    { question: 'Uchi Mata ', answer: 'Inner Thigh' },
    { question: 'Kosoto Gake ', answer: 'Minor Outer Hook' },
    { question: 'Tsuri Goshi ', answer: 'Lifting Hip' },
    { question: 'Yoko Otoshi ', answer: 'Side Drop' },
    { question: 'Ashi Guruma ', answer: 'Foot Wheel' },
    { question: 'Hane Goshi ', answer: 'Springing Hip' },
    { question: 'Harai Tsurikomi Ashi ', answer: 'Sweeping Lift-Pull Foot' },
    { question: 'Tomoe Nage ', answer: 'Stomach Throw' },
    { question: 'Kata Guruma ', answer: 'Shoulder Wheel' },
    { question: 'Sumi Gaeshi ', answer: 'Corner Reversal' },
    { question: 'Tani Otoshi ', answer: 'Valley Drop' },
    { question: 'Hane Makikomi ', answer: 'Springing Body Wrap' },
    { question: 'Sukui Nage ', answer: 'Scooping Throw' },
    { question: 'Utsuri Goshi ', answer: 'Transfer Hip' },
    { question: 'O Guruma ', answer: 'Major Wheel' },
    { question: 'Soto Makikomi ', answer: 'Outside Body Wrap' },
    { question: 'Uki Otoshi ', answer: 'Floating Drop' },
    { question: 'Osoto Guruma ', answer: 'Major Outer Wheel' },
    { question: 'Uki Waza ', answer: 'Floating Technique' },
    { question: 'Yoko Wakare ', answer: 'Side Separation' },
    { question: 'Yoko Guruma ', answer: 'Side Wheel' },
    { question: 'Ushiro Goshi ', answer: 'Rear Hip' },
    { question: 'Ura Nage ', answer: 'Back Throw' },
    { question: 'Sumi Otoshi ', answer: 'Corner Drop' },
    { question: 'Yoko Gake ', answer: 'Side Hook' },
]

export const chokes = [
      {
        "question": "Nami Juji Jime",
        "answer": "Normal Cross Choke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Kata Juji Jime",
        "answer": "Half Cross Choke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Gyaku Juji Jime",
        "answer": "Reverse Cross Choke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Hadaka Jime",
        "answer": "Naked Choke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Okuri Eri Jime",
        "answer": "Sliding Lapel Choke"
      },
      {
        "question": "Kata Ha Jime",
        "answer": "Single Wing Choke"
      }
    ]
    
export const pins = [
    {
    "question": "Kesa Gatame",
    "answer": "Scarf Hold"
    },
    {
    "question": "Kata Gatame",
    "answer": "Shoulder Hold"
    },
    {
    "question": "Tate Shiho Gatame",
    "answer": "Horizontal Four Quarter Hold"
    },
    {
    "question": "Yoko Shiho Gatame",
    "answer": "Side Hold"
    },
    {
    "question": "Kami Shiho Gatame",
    "answer": "Upper Four Corner Hold"
    },
    {
    "question": "Kuzure Kami Shiho Gatame",
    "answer": "Broken Upper Four Corner Hold"
    }
]

export const locks = [
    {
    "question": "Ude Garami",
    "answer": "Bent Arm Lock"
    },
    {
    "question": "Juji Gatame",
    "answer": "Cross Arm Lock"
    },
    {
    "question": "Ude Gatame",
    "answer": "Normal Arm Lock"
    },
    {
    "question": "Hiza Gatame",
    "answer": "Knee Arm Lock"
    }
]

export const questions = {
    locks, throws, pins, chokes
}